<rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>HN总结</title>
            <link>https://tg.i-c-a.su</link>
            <description>由大型语言模型编写的顶级 Hacker News 故事的自动摘要。</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:31:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体]欧洲有史以来最大的种子轮融资的接受者甚至没有产品</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30806</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338184" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">欧洲有史以来最大种子轮的接受者甚至没有产品</a><br />
法国初创公司 Mistral AI 已从 Lightspeed Venture Partners、Eric Sc​​hmidt 和 Xavier Niel 等投资者那里获得了 1.05 亿欧元（1.13 亿美元）的种子资金。这家总部位于巴黎的公司成立于四个星期前，刚刚开始招聘，估值为 2.4 亿欧元。 Mistral AI 的首席执行官 Arthur Mensch 是前谷歌 DeepMind 研究员，他与 Meta 校友 Timothée Lacroix 和 Guillaume Lample 共同创立了这家公司。该公司的网站称，它正在“组建一支世界级的团队来开发最好的人工智能生成模型”。根据科技投资追踪机构 <a href="https://tg.i-c-a.su/rss/Dealroom.co" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Dealroom.co 的数据，种子轮是欧洲有史以来最大的一轮</a>.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30806</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:31:19 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 公司表示，Twitter 以 94,000 美元的价格向博尔德办公室清洁工收费</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30805</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338234" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">公司表示，Twitter 以 94,000 美元的价格向 Boulder 办公室清洁工收取费用</一个<br />
Twitter 被总部位于博尔德的清洁公司 Avalanche Commercial Cleaning 起诉，指控其未能为 2022 年 10 月至 2022 年 12 月期间提供的清洁服务支付 93,504 美元。这起诉讼是在 Twitter 于 12 月被逐出其博尔德办公室并被指控拖欠 179,000 美元之后发起的欠房东 W.W. Reynolds Cos. Twitter 没有回应就诉讼发表评论的请求，但其公共关系部门自动回复了一封带有微笑便便表情符号的电子邮件，自 3 月以来，这一直是该公司对媒体询问的标准回应。<br />< br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30805</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:30:03 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>【媒体】美国要扼杀加密货币？</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30804</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338395" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">美国要扼杀加密吗？</a><br />
美国政府近期对加密货币公司提起的诉讼在业界引起了连锁反应。客户已提取数十亿美元，美国银行已限制与某些公司的合作，交易应用程序已停止列出某些资产。这导致一些人猜测美国正试图完全扼杀加密货币行业。然而，其他人则认为，这些诉讼只是规范行业和保护消费者的必要步骤。随着加密货币市场的不断发展，围绕这个问题的争议肯定会继续下去。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30804</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:29:51 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>像变形金刚一样思考 (pdf) (2021)</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30803</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36311871" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">像变形金刚一样思考 (pdf) (2021)</a>< br />
“像变形金刚一样思考”一书的作者提出了一种使用称为受限访问序列处理语言 (RASP) 的编程语言的变形编码器计算模型。他们将变换器编码器的基本组件、注意力和前馈计算映射到简单的原语中，并为变换器可以学习的任务提供 RASP 程序，例如直方图、排序和 Dyck 语言。作者还根据所需层数和注意力头数分析了这些任务的难度，并建议从它们的抽象中获得的见解可用于解释最近作品中出现的现象。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30803</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 约翰逊因 Partygate 故意误导国会议员而面临 90 天停职</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30802</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36337878" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">约翰逊因 Partygate 故意误导国会议员而面临 90 天停职</一个<br />
英国前首相鲍里斯·约翰逊因对派对门丑闻的处理引发争议而辞去国会议员职务。约翰逊因在这个问题上故意误导国会议员而面临议会停职 90 天的处罚，该问题涉及在唐宁街举行的封锁派对期间违反规则的指控。一些人猜测约翰逊可能在被推之前跳了下去，因为压力越来越大，要求他为自己的行为负责。 Partygate 丑闻震撼了英国政界，引发了对政府诚信的质疑。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30802</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:10:51 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体]减少摩擦</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30801</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36306337" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">减少摩擦</a><br />
<a href="https://tg.i-c-a.su/rss/ceejbot.com" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">ceejbot.com</a> 上的博文讨论了减少摩擦的重要性工程组织。作者将“过程”定义为习惯性的做事方式，将“摩擦”定义为推动项目前进所需的能量。该帖子探讨了减少摩擦的好处，并就如何做到这一点提供了具体建议。作者还谈到了对变革的潜在阻力，包括对过去解决方案的依恋、压力和习得性无助。该职位面向技术领导者，但对希望改进其工程组织工作的任何人都有帮助。 （根据 47% 的故事文本进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30801</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>【媒体】英格兰正面临迫在眉睫的水危机</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30800</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36337717" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">英国正面临迫在眉睫的水危机</a><br / >
由于供不应求，英格兰正面临迫在眉睫的水危机。尽管年平均降雨量为 1,100 毫米，但英国的大部分地区都在盯着一桶空水桶。在人口最集中的英格兰东南部，年平均降雨量在600毫米左右，与黎巴嫩或肯尼亚相当，比澳大利亚悉尼更干燥。政府数据显示，英国 28% 的地下水含水层和高达 18% 的河流和水库抽取的水量多于回流的水量。国家审计署预测，英格兰的总水需求将很快开始超过供应超过 2034。（根据 51% 的故事文本进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30800</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:57:22 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] Canva 宣布开发者平台和 5000 万美元的应用程序开发基金</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30799</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36337681" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Canva 宣布开发者平台和 5000 万美元的应用程序开发基金</一个<br />
Canva 推出了 Canva 开发者平台，其中包括一组 API 和开发工具，供开发者与 Canva 的 1.35 亿月活跃用户建立联系。该公司还设立了一个 5000 万美元的 Canva 开发者创新基金，以支持应用开发者在 Canva 应用市场上构建、发展和营销他们的应用。该基金将提供财政资助和专家指导，帮助开发者，尤其是来自弱势群体的开发者，将他们的应用程序概念转化为有形产品。 Canva 的生态系统负责人 Anwar Haneef 表示，该公司希望“构建、发现和使用简单的应用程序”。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30799</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:52:05 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 绕过 Bios 密码的硬件黑客攻击</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30798</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36337687" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">硬件黑客绕过 Bios 密码</a><br />
本文讨论了如何通过硬件破解绕过 Lenovo 笔记本电脑上的 BIOS 密码。作者发现了电可擦除可编程只读存储器 (EEPROM) 芯片中的一个漏洞，该芯片将 BIOS 配置与 BIOS 芯片本身分开存储。通过拦截或中断两个芯片之间的通信，可以绕过输入 BIOS 密码的提示。本文提供了有关如何识别易受攻击的芯片并执行攻击的分步指南。作者还分析了为什么这种攻击有效，并指出该过程可能不适用于所有 BIOS 模型。 （根据 89% 的故事文本进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30798</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:50:22 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 格拉斯哥惠灵顿公爵骑马雕像</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30797</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36337467" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">格拉斯哥惠灵顿公爵骑马雕像</a>< br />
苏格兰格拉斯哥的惠灵顿公爵骑马雕像是一座 A 类保护雕塑，自 1980 年代以来因公众将交通锥放在头上而闻名。 2013 年，格拉斯哥市议会提出了一项耗资 65,000 英镑的修复项目，其中包括将基座高度加倍以阻止破坏者，但该计划在公众反对后被撤回。雕像还安装了一个支持苏格兰独立公投的“是”锥体，一个金色锥体以庆祝苏格兰对 2012 年奥运会的贡献，以及一个带有乌克兰国旗颜色的锥体以支持乌克兰并作为抗议反对俄罗斯的入侵。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30797</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:44:08 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            </channel>
    </rss><rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>HN摘要</title>
            <link>https://tg.i-c-a.su</link>
            <description>大型语言模型编写的顶级黑客新闻故事的自动摘要。</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:54:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Show HN: Molly, a chatbot showing signs of consciousness</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30825</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338855" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Show HN: Molly, a chatbot showing signs of consciousness</a><br />
Molly is a conversational agent developed using OpenAI's Large Language Model (LLM) that has an inner monologue, giving the illusion of artificial consciousness. The experiment raises questions about the nature of consciousness and whether it can be learned or built into a machine. Attention Schema Theory, which postulates that consciousness is an illusion, is introduced as a theory of consciousness that shares similarities with illusionism. Molly is a prototype available for testing, and if Attention Schema Theory is correct, then Molly is technically conscious. The experiment shows that a machine can have an inner monologue that looks like consciousness, and raises concerns about how sentient beings should be treated.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30825</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:54:11 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Germany wants to legalize quality control of illegal drugs</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30824</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338870" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Germany wants to legalize quality control of illegal drugs</a><br />
Germany is considering legalizing drug-checking services, which would allow drug users to bring in illegal substances for quality control testing. The service would test for the components of drugs such as cocaine, heroin, ecstasy, and speed, as well as new psychoactive substances known as "bath salts." However, the service would not test for plant-based drugs like cannabis, medications, steroids, or potency drugs. The move is controversial, as it could be seen as condoning drug use, but proponents argue that it could help prevent overdoses and other health risks associated with unknown drug content.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30824</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:53:58 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Network of channels tried to saturate YouTube with pro-Bolsonaro content</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30823</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338902" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Network of channels tried to saturate YouTube with pro-Bolsonaro content</a><br />
A new report by researchers from the University of Exeter and Instituto Vero has identified a network of channels that attempted to saturate YouTube's recommender algorithm with pro-Bolsonaro content during the 2022 Brazil election. The study found that this influencer-driven content was promoted by mentions, tags, interviews, and cuts, and heavily contributed to the volume of recommended political videos and channels. Despite a balance in the number of videos between right- and left-leaning political camps, pro-Bolsonaro political narratives appeared to have been the most recommended by all five cluster channel groups. The report highlights the need to address the impact of influential platforms on people and society.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30823</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:53:44 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Video Ads Are Coming to All Your Uber Apps</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30822</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338456" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Video Ads Are Coming to All Your Uber Apps</a><br />
Uber is set to introduce video ads on all its apps, including Uber Eats, Drizly, and its ride-hailing app. The move is part of the company's strategy to boost ad sales and drive growth. The video ads will be long-form and will be displayed on the apps' home screens. The move has sparked controversy among some users who feel that the ads will be intrusive and disrupt their user experience. However, Uber is confident that the ads will be well-received and will help the company generate more revenue.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30822</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:43:27 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] The Guardian bans all gambling advertising</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30821</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338784" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">The Guardian bans all gambling advertising</a><br />
The Guardian has announced a global ban on all forms of gambling advertising, citing concerns over the industry's potential to cause addiction and financial ruin. The ban will apply worldwide to all of the company’s online and print outlets, including the Guardian, Observer, and Guardian Weekly. Lottery advertising has been excluded from the ban, with a spokesperson for the Guardian saying it could have social benefits through raising money for good causes. The decision to exclude gambling advertising from the Guardian’s publications follows the rapid growth of online betting on sporting events, aided by deregulation and the huge increase in the number of smartphone users.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30821</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:43:17 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] The myth of machine consciousness makes Narcissus of us all</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30820</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338614" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">The myth of machine consciousness makes Narcissus of us all</a><br />
The myth of Narcissus is particularly apt to our culture's relation to computers, especially in regard to those who believe that artificial intelligence will become conscious or that we will be able to upload our minds onto a digital platform. Computers produce a simulacrum of mental agency that sometimes fools us into thinking there must be someone there. However, computers work so well precisely because of the absence of mental features within them. The danger is not that the functions of our machines might become more like us, but rather that we might be progressively reduced to functions in a machine we can no longer control.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30820</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>The Instant Pot Failed Because It Was a Good Product</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30819</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338875" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">The Instant Pot Failed Because It Was a Good Product</a><br />
The Instant Pot, a popular kitchen gadget that promised to turn ingredients into family meals while you tend to other tasks, failed not because it was a bad product, but because it was too good. The device, which introduced the concept of at-home pressure cooking to many Americans, was a multi-cooker that slow-cooked, steamed, sautéed, cooked rice, and made yogurt. It was a useful, widely appreciated gadget that generated endless word-of-mouth praise and became a must-have kitchen sensation. However, the device's parent company, Instant Brands, failed to grow and expand the brand into other categories of household gadgetry, leading to bankruptcy.</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30819</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:32:50 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] The Ants and the Grasshopper</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30818</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338630" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">The Ants and the Grasshopper</a><br />
The article tells the story of the ants and the grasshopper, but with various twists and turns that explore different themes such as conditional philanthropy, bureaucracy, power, and the nature of progress. The ants initially refuse to help the grasshopper due to concerns about incentivizing procrastination, but eventually give in and feed it. This leads to a flood of requests for food, some of which are fraudulent, and the ants must set up a system for vetting claims. As their regulatory apparatus grows, they become consumed with overseeing the ecosystem and forget about producing food for themselves. The story ends with a futuristic twist, where a grasshopper's mind is stored in a colony of ants, waiting for the expansion of their hegemony to hit fundamental physical limits and for minds and civilizations to blossom out of cold computronium tiled across galaxies.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30818</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:23:29 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Multiple Connection Source Database With Prisma</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30817</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36336255" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Multiple Connection Source Database With Prisma</a><br />
The article discusses how to access two databases on different platforms in one application using Prisma. The author initially thought it would be easy with ORM, but found that Prisma only supports multiple schema in its official documentation. However, the author discovered a way to access both PostgreSQL and MySQL databases simultaneously using Prisma. The article provides a step-by-step guide on how to set up the project repository, prepare the databases, define the database connections, and fetch data from both sources. The article also includes code snippets and a folder structure example. (Summary based on 87% of story text.)<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30817</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:12:58 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Latency Testing Is Hard (RDNA 3 Power Saving)</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30816</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36336576" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Latency Testing Is Hard (RDNA 3 Power Saving)</a><br />
The author of this article discusses the challenges of latency testing, particularly in relation to AMD's RDNA 3 architecture and its power-saving techniques. The article compares the Infinity Cache latency between the RX 7900 XTX and the smaller RX 7600, noting that the power-saving strategy has different effects on the two implementations. The article also compares RDNA 3 to RDNA 2, finding that RDNA 3's Infinity Cache provides lower latency than its predecessor. The author concludes by acknowledging the difficulties of testing and encouraging readers to support their journalism.</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30816</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:12:46 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            </channel>
    </rss><?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>HN摘要</title>
            <link>https://tg.i-c-a.su</link>
            <description>大型语言模型编写的顶级黑客新闻故事的自动摘要。</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:18:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Cement's future could be a combination of Carbon Capture and Electrification</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30829</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36339253" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Cement's future could be a combination of Carbon Capture and Electrification</a><br />
Cement production is a major contributor to carbon emissions, with most of the emissions coming from chemical reactions that cannot be avoided. Carbon capture and storage (CCS) technology is seen as a potential solution, but it is controversial. The cement industry has been slow to adopt decarbonization technologies, but there are promising developments in electrification of process heat and new cement production processes. Startups like Coolbrook and SaltX are developing electric high-temperature heat technology, while Brimstone Energy and Sublime Systems are working on entirely new cement production processes. The combination of CCS with electrification appears to be one of the most promising options for the future of cement production.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30829</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:18:19 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Men who helped run Megaupload sentenced to prison in New Zealand</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30828</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338979" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Men who helped run Megaupload sentenced to prison in New Zealand</a><br />
Two former executives of the pirating website Megaupload have been sentenced to more than two years in prison by a New Zealand court. Mathias Ortmann and Bram van der Kolk had been fighting extradition to the US for 11 years on charges including racketeering. Last year, the men pleaded guilty to being part of a criminal group and causing artists to lose money by deception. The site, which was shut down by the FBI in 2012, is alleged to have made $175m from illegal downloads of films, music and television shows. Founder Kim Dotcom is continuing to fight extradition to the US.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30828</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:15:03 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Show HN: Multi Tenant SaaS Boilerplate</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30827</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36339135" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Show HN: Multi Tenant SaaS Boilerplate</a><br />
<a href="https://tg.i-c-a.su/rss/Volca.io" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Volca.io</a> has launched a new Multi Tenant SaaS Boilerplate that is built on a decoupled methodology and serverless stack. This platform is perfect for developers who want to create a multi-tenant SaaS application quickly and efficiently. The platform is designed to be highly scalable and secure, making it ideal for businesses of all sizes. The decoupled methodology and serverless stack have been praised by experts in the field, including Allan, a Principal Security Architect. This platform is a game-changer for developers who want to create SaaS applications that are both efficient and secure.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30827</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] JetPack Aviation (YC W19) Is Hiring</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30826</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36339236" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">JetPack Aviation (YC W19) Is Hiring</a><br />
JetPack Aviation, a venture-backed aviation startup and YCombinator alumni, is seeking a Chief Engineer to lead their engineering organization. The company has developed the world's only successful turbine powered Jetpack and is now working on the Speeder Air Utility Vehicle (AUV), which will be the smallest and fastest, heavy-lift turbine powered VTOL aircraft ever designed. The successful candidate should have 10+ years of progressive experience in building an aerospace program, 3-5+ years in senior leadership roles, and the ability to attract top talent across engineering disciplines. The company values teamwork, innovation, and individuality and is an equal opportunity employer.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30826</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Show HN: Molly, a chatbot showing signs of consciousness</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30825</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338855" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Show HN: Molly, a chatbot showing signs of consciousness</a><br />
Molly is a conversational agent developed using OpenAI's Large Language Model (LLM) that has an inner monologue, giving the illusion of artificial consciousness. The experiment raises questions about the nature of consciousness and whether it can be learned or built into a machine. Attention Schema Theory, which postulates that consciousness is an illusion, is introduced as a theory of consciousness that shares similarities with illusionism. Molly is a prototype available for testing, and if Attention Schema Theory is correct, then Molly is technically conscious. The experiment shows that a machine can have an inner monologue that looks like consciousness, and raises concerns about how sentient beings should be treated.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30825</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:54:11 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Germany wants to legalize quality control of illegal drugs</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30824</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338870" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Germany wants to legalize quality control of illegal drugs</a><br />
Germany is considering legalizing drug-checking services, which would allow drug users to bring in illegal substances for quality control testing. The service would test for the components of drugs such as cocaine, heroin, ecstasy, and speed, as well as new psychoactive substances known as "bath salts." However, the service would not test for plant-based drugs like cannabis, medications, steroids, or potency drugs. The move is controversial, as it could be seen as condoning drug use, but proponents argue that it could help prevent overdoses and other health risks associated with unknown drug content.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30824</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:53:58 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Network of channels tried to saturate YouTube with pro-Bolsonaro content</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30823</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338902" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Network of channels tried to saturate YouTube with pro-Bolsonaro content</a><br />
A new report by researchers from the University of Exeter and Instituto Vero has identified a network of channels that attempted to saturate YouTube's recommender algorithm with pro-Bolsonaro content during the 2022 Brazil election. The study found that this influencer-driven content was promoted by mentions, tags, interviews, and cuts, and heavily contributed to the volume of recommended political videos and channels. Despite a balance in the number of videos between right- and left-leaning political camps, pro-Bolsonaro political narratives appeared to have been the most recommended by all five cluster channel groups. The report highlights the need to address the impact of influential platforms on people and society.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30823</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:53:44 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Video Ads Are Coming to All Your Uber Apps</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30822</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338456" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Video Ads Are Coming to All Your Uber Apps</a><br />
Uber is set to introduce video ads on all its apps, including Uber Eats, Drizly, and its ride-hailing app. The move is part of the company's strategy to boost ad sales and drive growth. The video ads will be long-form and will be displayed on the apps' home screens. The move has sparked controversy among some users who feel that the ads will be intrusive and disrupt their user experience. However, Uber is confident that the ads will be well-received and will help the company generate more revenue.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30822</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:43:27 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] The Guardian bans all gambling advertising</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30821</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338784" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">The Guardian bans all gambling advertising</a><br />
The Guardian has announced a global ban on all forms of gambling advertising, citing concerns over the industry's potential to cause addiction and financial ruin. The ban will apply worldwide to all of the company’s online and print outlets, including the Guardian, Observer, and Guardian Weekly. Lottery advertising has been excluded from the ban, with a spokesperson for the Guardian saying it could have social benefits through raising money for good causes. The decision to exclude gambling advertising from the Guardian’s publications follows the rapid growth of online betting on sporting events, aided by deregulation and the huge increase in the number of smartphone users.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30821</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:43:17 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] The myth of machine consciousness makes Narcissus of us all</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30820</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36338614" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">The myth of machine consciousness makes Narcissus of us all</a><br />
The myth of Narcissus is particularly apt to our culture's relation to computers, especially in regard to those who believe that artificial intelligence will become conscious or that we will be able to upload our minds onto a digital platform. Computers produce a simulacrum of mental agency that sometimes fools us into thinking there must be someone there. However, computers work so well precisely because of the absence of mental features within them. The danger is not that the functions of our machines might become more like us, but rather that we might be progressively reduced to functions in a machine we can no longer control.<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30820</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:33:00 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            </channel>
    </rss>