<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>HN总结</title>
            <link>https://tg.i-c-a.su</link>
            <description>由大型语言模型编写的顶级 Hacker News 故事的自动摘要。</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:16:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>获取 10TB 的 GitHub 日志并提取所有用户和存储库的详细信息</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30854</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36341160" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">获取 10TB 的 GitHub 日志并提取所有用户和存储库的详细信息< /一个<br />
这篇博文的作者讨论了他们如何使用 Trickest 的工作流方法来解析超过 10TB 的 GitHub 日志，从所有用户和存储库中提取公共详细信息。作者解释了这项任务的重要性，因为 GitHub 体现了一个充满活力、不断发展的开发人员及其项目生态系统。通过解析这些数据，他们能够生成从 2015 年至今的所有用户和存储库的综合列表。作者还讨论了他们在解析如此庞大的数据集时所面临的挑战以及他们是如何克服这些挑战的。最后，作者邀请读者访问他们收集的数据。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30854</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:16:25 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 火星毅力号探测器内部闪光灯的最新细节</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30853</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36339487" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">火星毅力号探测器内部闪光灯的最新细节</a ><br />
Phison 是火星毅力号火星车内部 8GB 工业级 PSS4A111-8G uSSD 的制造商，它分享了有关闪光灯在火星车照片处理、存储和传输系统中的使用的最新细节。 Phison SSD 被用作音频和图片/视频数据的缓冲器，如果它发生故障，流动站的成像系统将停止工作。 Phison 还透露，Perseverance 有一个由英特尔凌动 E3845 处理器控制的数据存储单元 (DSU)，配备 8GB DRAM，安装在 Compulab COMEX IE38 主板上。 Phison SSD 还参与了其他太空任务，包括 Lonestar Data Holdings 的月球数据中心任务。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30853</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:10:07 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>PostgreSQL 文档和社区的局限性</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30852</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36328466" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">PostgreSQL 文档和社区的局限性</a><br />
根据作者的说法，PostgreSQL 文档既好又差，这取决于它的制作过程。文档存储在与源代码相同的 git 存储库中，这意味着更新由熟悉代码更改的开发人员进行，从而产生极其准确的文档。然而，更新文档成为一项必须完成的任务，这样代码才能提交，如果对文档的更改是有益的但与任何特定补丁无关，则不太可能完成。对文档的结构更改通常是有争议的，并且比新参数或新 SQL 命令的文档条目需要更多的工作才能得到落实。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30852</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:09:52 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] Unihiker，一款 80 美元的单板 PC，带有 2.</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30851</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36341287" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Unihiker，一款售价 80 美元的单板 PC，带有 2.8 英寸触摸屏，四边形-内核 ARM Cortex-A35</a><br />
UNIHIKER 是一款售价 80 美元的单板计算机，配备 2.8 英寸触摸屏、Wi-Fi 和蓝牙。它还具有光传感器、加速度计、陀螺仪和麦克风，并且可以与各种传感器和执行器通信。预装的软件使入门变得容易，Jupyter Notebook 允许使用智能手机或平板电脑进行编程。 UNIHIKER 支持 VS Code、VIM 和 Thonny，PinPong 控制库允许使用 Python 直接控制传感器和执行器。内置的物联网服务允许在设备上进行实时网络数据访问和数据存储。 UNIHIKER 为学习、编码和创作提供紧凑、功能丰富且用户友好的开发体验。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30851</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:06:36 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 谷歌警告自己的员工不要使用来自聊天机器人的代码输入数据</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30850</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36341188" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Google 警告自己的员工不要使用来自聊天机器人的代码输入数据</a><br />
谷歌的母公司 Alphabet 已警告其员工不要将机密材料输入人工智能聊天机器人，包括其自己的 Bard 程序，因为存在泄露风险。该公司还建议其工程师避免直接使用聊天机器人可以生成的计算机代码。这些担忧反映了公司警告员工不要使用公开可用的聊天程序的安全标准。世界各地越来越多的企业已经在人工智能聊天机器人上设置了防护栏，包括三星、亚马逊、德意志银行，据报道还有苹果。截至 1 月，约 43% 的专业人士在使用 ChatGPT 或其他人工智能工具，而且通常没有告诉他们的老板。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30850</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:58:13 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Zluda：在英特尔 GPU 上运行 CUDA 代码，未修改</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30849</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36341211" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Zluda：在英特尔 GPU 上运行 CUDA 代码，未修改</a> <br />
ZLUDA 是一个允许未经修改的 CUDA 应用程序以接近本机的性能在英特尔 GPU 上运行的项目。它是英特尔 GPU 上 CUDA 的直接替代品，可与当前集成的英特尔 UHD GPU 和未来的英特尔 Xe GPU 配合使用。该项目是一个概念证明，目前还不完整且存在错误。 ZLUDA 性能已经在 Intel UHD 630 上用 GeekBench 5.2.3 进行了测量，结果表明它可以接近类似编写的 OpenCL 代码的性能。 ZLUDA 不同于 AMD HIP 或 Intel DPC++ 兼容性工具包等其他移植工具包，因为它不需要任何程序员的努力来将应用程序移植到 API。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30849</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:47:56 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体]考古学家发现3000年前的宝剑，保存异常完好</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30848</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340671" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">考古学家发现一把 3000 年前的剑，保存完好</一个<br />
巴伐利亚州诺德林根的考古学家发现了一把拥有 3000 年历史的青铜剑，该剑保存完好。据信，八角形刀柄的八角形剑出自公元前 14 世纪末的青铜时代中期。这个时代出土的刀剑非常罕见，它们要么来自 19 世纪故意打开的墓葬，要么是个别的、推测为祭祀的出土物。这把剑是在一个男人、女人和青年的坟墓中发现的，但不清楚他们之间有什么关系。剑和葬将进一步检查。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30848</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:46:41 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] Show HN：Agency——用 Python 统一人类、AI 和其他计算系统</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30847</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36326587" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">显示 HN：机构——统一人类、人工智能和其他计算系统, 在 Python 中</a><br />
Agency 是一个 Python 库，它为集成 AI 代理、人类和传统计算系统提供了一个通用的通信和操作框架。它允许建立称为“空间”的共享环境，在该环境中，任意数量的代理都可以像可以执行操作的单个代理一样平等地相互称呼。该库处理通用消息传递协议的细节，并允许发现和调用所有各方的操作，自动处理报告异常、强制访问限制等事情。 API 允许代理与各种系统集成，如 UI 驱动的应用程序、终端环境、软件 API、其他 AI 代理、人员和其他任何东西。 （根据 45% 的故事文本进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30847</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:42:26 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 矩阵食谱 [pdf](https://news.</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30846</link>
                <description><br />矩阵食谱 [pdf](<a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340930" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">https://news.ycombinator .com/item?id=36340930</a>)<br />
矩阵食谱是关于矩阵和相关事物的事实、恒等式、近似值、不等式和关系的集合。对于任何使用矩阵代数、矩阵关系、矩阵恒等式、行列式的导数和逆矩阵等的人来说，它都是一个快速的桌面参考。内容会持续更新并定期更新，欢迎提出额外内容或主题阐述的建议。该食谱包括对贡献者和来源的致谢，以及可能存在错误和失误的免责声明。内容涵盖基础知识、导数、逆矩阵、复矩阵、解和分解、统计和概率、特殊矩阵和函数。 （根据故事文本的 6% 进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30846</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:38:13 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>【媒体】中国再次降息 青年失业率创新高</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30845</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340794" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">随着青年失业率创历史新高，中国再次降息</a ><br />
中国已将其关键政策利率，即中期贷款利率，从 2.75% 下调至 2.65%，这是本周第二次降息，此前一系列官方数据描绘了世界第二大经济体在 Covid 后复苏的悲观景象经济。此举将增加银行系统的流动性并降低短期贷款的成本，因为官员们继续努力提振萎靡不振的经济。新的政府数据显示，5 月份零售额同比增长 12.7%，但低于上月 18.4% 的增幅，也低于经济学家的预期。与此同时，5月份城市青年失业率再创新高，达到20.8%。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30845</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            </channel>
    </rss><?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>HN摘要</title>
            <link>https://tg.i-c-a.su</link>
            <description>大型语言模型编写的顶级黑客新闻故事的自动摘要。</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:17:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>UnsuckJS: Progressively enhance HTML with lightweight JavaScript libraries</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30870</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36343544" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">UnsuckJS: Progressively enhance HTML with lightweight JavaScript libraries</a><br />
UnsuckJS offers a variety of lightweight JavaScript libraries for progressively enhancing HTML and building fast, reactive web components without virtual DOM overhead or build tools. The libraries include Lit, htmx, diffHTML, and more, each with their own unique features and benefits. Some libraries, like Ben's DOM Clobberer and the 6kb subset of Vue, are optimized for progressive enhancement, while others like Microhydration and the reactive Web Component library offer declarative creation of browser-native web components. Overall, UnsuckJS provides a range of options for developers looking to improve their web development process.</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30870</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:17:07 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Getting to Know the Right People</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30869</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36323888" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Getting to Know the Right People</a><br />
The author discusses the challenge of finding good people in areas where one lacks expertise, such as finding a good plumber or making new friends in a new city. They suggest that the key to finding the right people is to know the right people, and that the best way to connect to a new network is to bootstrap it from another network. The author acknowledges that some networks may be exclusive and not accessible to everyone, which is a major source of inequality. They also provide tips for making connections and building networks, including joining professional groups and using social media to make friends. (Summary based on 88% of story text.)</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30869</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:11:52 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Declining Quality of Google Is an Opportunity for Reddit and Other Competitors</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30868</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36343143" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Declining Quality of Google Is an Opportunity for Reddit and Other Competitors</a><br />
The ongoing Reddit blackout in protest of Reddit’s API pricing has had an unexpected victim: Google. Similar to Wikipedia, Google drives a lot of traffic to Reddit from people using Google indirectly as a Reddit search engine. However, the quality of Google’s search results has declined over the years, with many people resorting to hacks such as appending “Reddit” or “Wikipedia” to search queries or using lesser-known search engines. Two key problems with Google search, stale results and vague/irrelevant results, could be capitalized on by competitors like Reddit, Microsoft, or Open AI. Reddit's user-generated content could be monetized or licensed, or a landing page could be created that incorporates Reddit user-contributed content.</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30868</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:06:36 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Let's Encrypt Acme API Outage</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30867</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36342808" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Let's Encrypt Acme API Outage</a><br />
Let's Encrypt is experiencing an outage with their Production ACME API and has temporarily stopped issuing certificates. The issue is being investigated and updates will be provided as they become available. This may cause inconvenience for those who rely on Let's Encrypt for their website security.</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30867</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:48:12 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Parallel futures in mobile application development</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30866</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340925" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Parallel futures in mobile application development</a><br />
The article explores different options for mobile application development frameworks, including Ionic/Capacitor, React Native, NativeScript, Flutter, and Ark. The author discusses the benefits and drawbacks of each framework, as well as the language choices that come with them. They also delve into the possibility of using Rust as a language for mobile app development, as well as the potential for a "Flutter-ized" web using WebAssembly, WebGPU, WebHID, and ARIA. The article offers a thought-provoking exploration of the different paths that mobile app development could take in the future. (Summary based on 50% of story text.)<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30866</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:47:02 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Sequence diagrams, the only good thing UML brought to software development</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30865</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36342931" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Sequence diagrams, the only good thing UML brought to software development</a><br />
The article on <a href="https://tg.i-c-a.su/rss/mermaidchart.com" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">mermaidchart.com</a> argues that sequence diagrams are the only good thing that came out of the now-dead Unified Modelling Language (UML) from the late 1990s. The article provides a brief history of UML and explains why sequence diagrams survived despite most of UML getting consigned to the dustbin of software history. The article also explains the primary use cases for sequence diagrams and provides tips on how to design them effectively. The author argues that sequence diagrams are underrated and underused and that they are an ideal use case for MermaidChart because it allows users to choose informal simplicity over the rigid complexity that results from using older tools like IBM’s Rational Rose. (Summary based on 87% of story text.)<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30865</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:37:42 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] A Storefront for Robots</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30864</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340695" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">A Storefront for Robots</a><br />
Get Bullish, an online store for kitschy, snarky, and quirky gifts, is just one of many small businesses struggling with the ins and outs of Google's search algorithm. The store's blog posts are generated using artificial intelligence tools and packed with SEO keywords and phrases to act as a funnel for consumers coming from Google Search. The text is largely intended to be read by Google's web crawlers rather than human customers. While optimizing content for Google is a non-negotiable chore for small business owners, it has also led to the degradation of Google's biggest product, Search, over time. (Summary based on 47% of story text.)<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30864</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Career Progression</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30863</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36323044" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Career Progression</a><br />
The author of this article reflects on their recent promotion to Principal Engineer and the concept of career ladders and titles in the tech industry. They express skepticism about reducing individuals to points on a number line and the flaws in measuring individuals based on titles. However, they also acknowledge that titles can correct for biases and compensation disparities. The author shares a personal experience of being denied a promotion despite meeting the rubric for the position and highlights the flaws in technical interviews as a measure of talent. They ultimately conclude that titles and career ladders are a social construct that changes with organizational culture and that there is always more to learn from colleagues, regardless of their position on the ladder.</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30863</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:10:02 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Have You Been to the Library Lately?</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30862</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340548" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Have You Been to the Library Lately?</a><br />
The role of public libraries has evolved significantly in recent years, with many libraries now serving as a last resort for vulnerable populations, including the homeless. In response to this, many libraries have begun hiring in-house social workers to provide support to those in need. However, library workers across Canada report being attacked, threatened, and sexually assaulted, and many feel ill-equipped to handle the complex needs of their patrons. Despite these challenges, libraries remain a vital public space, providing access to resources and programming on a wide range of topics. Calgary Public Library, in particular, has gained recognition for its innovative social programs and stunning architecture. (Summary based on 38% of story text.)<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30862</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:05:48 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[Media] Abrupt expansion of climate change risks for species globally</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30861</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340591" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Abrupt expansion of climate change risks for species globally</a><br />
A new study published in the journal Science warns of an abrupt expansion of climate change risks for species globally. The study highlights the widespread declines among bumblebees across continents, rapid warming associated with population decline among terrestrial birds and mammals globally, and greater vulnerability to warming of marine versus terrestrial ectotherms. The study also suggests that species better track climate warming in the oceans than on land. The projected effect on insects, vertebrates, and plants of limiting global warming to 1.5 °C rather than 2 °C is also discussed. The study concludes that accelerating extinction risk from climate change is a major concern. (Summary based on 39% of story text.)<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30861</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:53:30 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            </channel>
    </rss><?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>HN总结</title>
            <link>https://tg.i-c-a.su</link>
            <description>由大型语言模型编写的顶级 Hacker News 故事的自动摘要。</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:30:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] Google Lens 现在可让您自我诊断皮肤状况</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30873</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36342882" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Google Lens 现在可让您自我诊断皮肤状况</a> <br />
Google Lens 添加了一项新功能，允许用户通过扫描皮肤、头发或指甲的任何变化来识别皮肤状况。该应用程序可用于拍照或上传照片，然后识别与搜索相关的视觉匹配项。然而，虽然该功能是一个有用的工具，但它不能替代专业的医疗建议，如果用户担心皮肤状况或任何其他健康问题，应始终咨询医疗保健专业人员。<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30873</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:30:59 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>科学彩色地图</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30872</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36342785" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">科学彩色地图</a><br />
<a href="https://tg.i-c-a.su/rss/www.fabiocrameri.ch" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">www.fabiocrameri.ch</a> 网站提供一系列科学可以与各种软件程序一起使用的彩色地图，包括 MatLab、Python 和 Adob​​e Photoshop。这些地图的设计具有视觉吸引力和易于解释的特点，使其可用于广泛的科学应用。该网站还提供特定软件程序的额外格式，以及 GPlates 的便利包。颜色映射几乎内置于所有内容中，并且专为构建器设计。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30872</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:30:48 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 辐射生物学可以帮助减少对低水平辐射的严重恐惧</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30871</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36342426" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">辐射生物学可以帮助减少对低水平辐射的极度恐惧</一个<br />
自 75 多年前原子时代开始以来，辐射恐惧症或对辐射的恐惧就愈演愈烈。这种恐惧常常成为安全和有益地使用辐射和放射性物质的障碍。然而，清楚地了解当前的科学知识和对辐射暴露影响的理解可能有助于减轻对辐射的一些恐惧。在这份手稿中，作者解决了他们认为导致辐射恐惧的几个问题，并审查了可用于解决这些问题的研究数据。作者希望这将有助于减轻公众对低剂量辐射的恐惧，并证明这种恐惧并非基于科学知识和理解。 （根据故事文本的 12% 进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30871</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:25:31 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>UnsuckJS：使用轻量级 JavaScript 库逐步增强 HTML</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30870</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36343544" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">UnsuckJS：使用轻量级 JavaScript 库逐步增强 HTML</a>< br />
UnsuckJS 提供各种轻量级 JavaScript 库，用于逐步增强 HTML 和构建快速、反应性的 Web 组件，而无需虚拟 DOM 开销或构建工具。这些库包括 Lit、htmx、diffHTML 等，每个库都有自己独特的功能和优势。一些库，如 Ben 的 DOM Clobberer 和 Vue 的 6kb 子集，针对渐进增强进行了优化，而其他库，如 Microhydration 和反应式 Web 组件库，则提供浏览器原生 Web 组件的声明式创建。总的来说，UnsuckJS 为希望改进 Web 开发过程的开发人员提供了一系列选择。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30870</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:17:07 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>认识合适的人</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30869</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36323888" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">结识合适的人</a><br />
作者讨论了在缺乏专业知识的领域寻找优秀人才的挑战，例如寻找优秀的管道工或在新城市结交新朋友。他们建议找到合适的人的关键是认识合适的人，而连接到新网络的最佳方式是从另一个网络引导它。作者承认，某些网络可能是排他性的，并非所有人都可以访问，这是不平等的一个主要来源。他们还提供建立联系和建立网络的技巧，包括加入专业团体和使用社交媒体结交朋友。 （根据 88% 的故事文本进行总结。）</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30869</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:11:52 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>谷歌质量下降是 Reddit 和其他竞争对手的机会</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30868</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36343143" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">谷歌质量下降是 Reddit 和其他竞争对手的机会</一个<br />
为抗议 Reddit 的 API 定价而持续进行的 Reddit 停电有一个意想不到的受害者：谷歌。与维基百科类似，谷歌为 Reddit 带来了大量流量，这些流量来自间接将谷歌用作 Reddit 搜索引擎的人们。然而，谷歌搜索结果的质量多年来一直在下降，许多人诉诸黑客手段，例如在搜索查询中附加“Reddit”或“维基百科”或使用鲜为人知的搜索引擎。谷歌搜索的两个关键问题，陈旧的结果和模糊/不相关的结果，可以被 Reddit、微软或 Open AI 等竞争对手利用。 Reddit 的用户生成内容可以货币化或获得许可，或者可以创建包含 Reddit 用户贡献内容的登录页面。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30868</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:06:36 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>让我们加密 Acme API 中断</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30867</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36342808" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">让我们加密 Acme API 中断</a><br />
Let's Encrypt 的 Production ACME API 出现故障，并暂时停止颁发证书。该问题正在调查中，并将在可用时提供更新。这可能会给那些依赖 Let's Encrypt 来确保网站安全的人带来不便。</description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30867</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:48:12 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体]移动应用开发的平行未来</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30866</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340925" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">移动应用程序开发的平行未来</a><br />
本文探讨了移动应用程序开发框架的不同选择，包括 Ionic/Capacitor、React Native、NativeScript、Flutter 和 Ark。作者讨论了每个框架的优点和缺点，以及它们附带的语言选择。他们还研究了使用 Rust 作为移动应用程序开发语言的可能性，以及使用 WebAssembly、WebGPU、WebHID 和 ARIA 的“Flutter 化”网络的潜力。这篇文章对移动应用程序开发在未来可能采取的不同路径进行了发人深省的探索。 （根据故事文本的 50% 进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30866</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:47:02 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 时序图，UML 给软件开发带来的唯一好东西</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30865</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36342931" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">时序图，UML给软件开发带来的唯一好处</一个<br />
<a href="https://tg.i-c-a.su/rss/mermaidchart.com" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">mermaidchart.com</a> 上的文章认为序列图是唯一好的从 1990 年代末期现在已经过时的统一建模语言 (UML) 中产生的东西。这篇文章提供了 UML 的简要历史，并解释了为什么尽管大多数 UML 被扔进了软件历史的垃圾箱，但序列图仍然存在。本文还解释了序列图的主要用例，并提供了有关如何有效设计它们的技巧。作者认为序列图被低估和未充分利用，它们是 MermaidChart 的理想用例，因为它允许用户选择非正式的简单性，而不是使用 IBM 的 Rational Rose 等旧工具所导致的严格复杂性。 （根据 87% 的故事文本进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30865</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:37:42 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>[媒体] 机器人店面</title>
                <link>https://t.me/hn_summary/30864</link>
                <description><br /><a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=36340695" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">机器人店面</a><br />
Get Bullish 是一家出售俗气、刻薄和古怪礼物的在线商店，它只是众多在谷歌搜索算法的来龙去脉中苦苦挣扎的小企业之一。该商店的博客文章是使用人工智能工具生成的，并包含 SEO 关键字和短语，作为来自 Google 搜索的消费者的渠道。该文本主要供 Google 的网络爬虫而非人类客户阅读。虽然为谷歌优化内容对于小企业主来说是一件没有商量余地的苦差事，但随着时间的推移，它也导致了谷歌最大的产品搜索的退化。 （根据 47% 的故事文本进行总结。）<br /><br /></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://t.me/hn_summary/30864</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            </channel>
    </rss>