<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>编辑：私人</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/new</link>
            <description>作为第 3 方 Reddit API 抗议的一部分，此 subreddit 是私有的。请不要发消息要求访问，访问将在抗议结束后恢复。更多信息在这里：https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-65855608</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:18:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </channel>
    </rss><?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss version="2.0">
        <channel>
            <title>最新提交：编辑</title>
            <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/new</link>
            <description>作为第三方Reddit API抗议活动的一部分，该subreddit是私人的。请不要留言以访问访问，访问将在抗议结束时恢复。更多信息在这里：https：//www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-65855608</description>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:23:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>Regular Mod request of our professionals: Please check-in and give advice to the people who post on the "Ask Anything" and "Career" threads.Announcements</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a7lfl/regular_mod_request_of_our_professionals_please/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>We get loads of professionals accessing this subreddit - along with lots of people <em>trying to become professionals</em> in the field.</p> <p>We're asking our professionals to <em>once a week</em>, check in on our &quot;Ask anything&quot; and &quot;Career&quot; threads, and provide help!</p> <p>These can be found on the menu area of the subreddit on new Reddit or via the official client.</p> <h2>Just to be clear - We're talking from the Weekly Links at the top of the sub.</h2> <p><a href="https://i.imgur.com/I19zmc2.png">https://i.imgur.com/I19zmc2.png</a></p> <p>The idea is that <strong>you</strong> go in there and provide helpful advice for the:</p> <ul> <li>&quot;Ask anything&quot; crowd</li> <li>People looking for career advice.</li> </ul> <p>Thank you (not here, those threads please!)</p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <p><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/search?q=Megathread%20monday&amp;restrict_sr=1&amp;sort=new">Ask anything threads</a></p> <p><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/search/?q=Career%20Advice%20Sat&amp;restrict_sr=1&amp;sort=new">Career threads</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator"> /u/AutoModerator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a7lfl/regular_mod_request_of_our_professionals_please/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a7lfl/regular_mod_request_of_our_professionals_please/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a7lfl/regular_mod_request_of_our_professionals_please/</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:00:30 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Please Read: We're Reopening - but we want to provide context to the Blackout (both here and across Reddit)</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a6wqq/please_read_were_reopening_but_we_want_to_provide/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><h2>TL;DR</h2> <p>We apologize for the blackout; it was part of a larger attempt to protest against a corporation profiting off our engagement. Although it showed Reddit's shortcomings, it wasn't as effective as intended - which we were aware of at the start. And, rather than abandoning Reddit (or closing the community), <a href="https://discord.gg/mfweGwhG">we're diversifying by opening a Discord server</a> for Post Professionals and aspiring professionals. </p> <h2>Details</h2> <p>If you're not paying, you're the product, and Reddit, like others, often disregards its users. With an upcoming IPO, Reddit's actions have affected third-party tools, <em>including those essential for vision-impaired users</em>, due to high API pricing changes and a rapid rollout of changes. These pricing changes are crucial to show value for the IPO - since many AI models use Reddit's data for training.</p> <p>These abrupt alterations show Reddit's neglect of user needs and push for investor appeal. The CEO's lack of transparency and minimal response in an AMA further exacerbate user alienation.</p> <p>Just like Facebook and Twitter, Reddit views users as profit obstacles, not partners. This matters because every subreddit depends on volunteers so Reddit can profit from user-created material. The third-party tools provide access to vision-impaired users along with fulfilling broken promises for better moderation tools.</p> <p>Reddit could buy these tools, develop effective code quickly, roll out their API at a sensible pace, or create a distinct API for trusted tools. However, they refuse any plan and ignore users' dissatisfaction. </p> <p>Understand that being the product in social media means your needs may be overlooked, as demonstrated by Reddit.</p> <p>We recommend these insightful Reddit threads:</p> <ul> <li><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ModCoord/comments/149h75d/reddit_ceo_steve_huffmans_thirdparty_api_debacle/">Reddit CEO's Third-Party API Debacle and the Importance of Honesty</a></li> <li><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ModCoord/comments/149of0x/on_trust_as_a_business_asset_and_why_reddit/">Trust as a Business Asset: Reddit's Missteps</a></li> <li><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ModCoord/comments/149apf9/campaigns_have_notched_slightly_lower_impression/">Effects of the Blackout on Campaign Impressions</a></li> </ul> <p>Several subreddits, including <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/aww">/r/aww</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/videos">/r/videos</a> and <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Apple">/r/Apple</a>, have disappeared indefinitely due to these issues. <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ModCoord/comments/148ks6u/indefinite_blackout_next_steps_polling_your/jo0pqzk/">The list of key points are here</a>.</p> <p>We understand the importance of our subreddits to you, <a href="https://discord.gg/mfweGwhG">so we're expanding to Discord</a>, a space for professional discussions and networking. Though different from Reddit, it's a step towards diversification.</p> <p>We're not leaving Reddit, but it's essential to highlight the platform's issues. <a href="https://discord.gg/mfweGwhG">Join us on Discord</a>, engage here, and support initiatives that promote online accessibility and inclusion.</p> <p>Thank you for your support.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/greenysmac"> /u/greenysmac </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a6wqq/please_read_were_reopening_but_we_want_to_provide/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a6wqq/please_read_were_reopening_but_we_want_to_provide/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14a6wqq/please_read_were_reopening_but_we_want_to_provide/</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:32:14 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Tip Thursday! Week of Thu Jun 15</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/149xddy/tip_thursday_week_of_thu_jun_15/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><h1>Have you learned something new/cool (or maybe just obvious) in the past week?</h1> <p>Put your tool **in brackets [Avid, Premiere, FCPX, After Effects, Resolve] and the description following that.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator"> /u/AutoModerator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/149xddy/tip_thursday_week_of_thu_jun_15/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/149xddy/tip_thursday_week_of_thu_jun_15/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/149xddy/tip_thursday_week_of_thu_jun_15/</guid>
                <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Ask a Pro - WEEKLY - Monday Mon Jun 12, 2023 - No Stupid Questions! THIS IS WHERE YOU POST if you don't do this for a living! RULES + Career Questions?</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147j9qy/ask_a_pro_weekly_monday_mon_jun_12_2023_no_stupid/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><h1><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors">/r/editors</a> is a community for professionals in post-production.</h1> <p>Every week, we use this thread for open discussion for anyone with questions about editing or post-production, **regardless of your profession or professional status.** </p> <p><strong>Again, If you're new here, know that this subreddit is targeted for professionals. Our mod team prunes the subreddit and posts novice level questions here.</strong> </p> <p>&#x200b;</p> <h1>If you're not sure what category you fall into? This is the thread you're looking for.</h1> <h1>Key rules: Be excellent (and patient) with one another. No self-promotion. No piracy. [The rest of the rules are found here](<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/about/rules/">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/about/rules/</a>)</h1> <p>If you don't work in this field, this is where your question should go</p> <p>What sort of questions is fair game for this thread? </p> <ul> <li>Is school worth it?</li> <li>Career question?</li> <li>Which editor *should you pay for?* (free tools? see <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/videoediting">/r/videoediting</a>)</li> <li>Thinking about a side hustle?</li> <li>What should I set my rates at? (SEE WIKI) </li> <li>Graduating from school? and need <em>getting started</em> advice?</li> </ul> <p>&#x200b;</p> <p><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/wiki/index">There's a wiki for this sub.</a> Feel free to suggest pages it needs.</p> <p>We have a sister subreddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/videoediting">/r/videoediting</a>. It's ideal if you're not making a living at this - but this thread is for everyone!</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator"> /u/AutoModerator </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147j9qy/ask_a_pro_weekly_monday_mon_jun_12_2023_no_stupid/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147j9qy/ask_a_pro_weekly_monday_mon_jun_12_2023_no_stupid/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147j9qy/ask_a_pro_weekly_monday_mon_jun_12_2023_no_stupid/</guid>
                <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Adobe premiere sequences are messed up when using multiple computers</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147antu/adobe_premiere_sequences_are_messed_up_when_using/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>So I do my edit on my sequence, and then I want to send the whole project over to another editor to cut short promos from my main sequence. I save a copy of the project file and transfer everything to the other editor, but when they open and relink the media all of the clips look like they are slipped and out of time with the audio. The sequences themselves looks just like my edit but something is wrong here and I am stumped. Any help is appreciated.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/the_mighty_jibbick"> /u/the_mighty_jibbick </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147antu/adobe_premiere_sequences_are_messed_up_when_using/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147antu/adobe_premiere_sequences_are_messed_up_when_using/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/147antu/adobe_premiere_sequences_are_messed_up_when_using/</guid>
                <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:53:55 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Does anyone have a mouse with multiple buttons? I have a Logitech Hero g502. It has 13 buttons. What shortcuts do you use on your mouse? I'd like to read them and see what shortcut they might be useful to me.</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14792th/does_anyone_have_a_mouse_with_multiple_buttons_i/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>I have 13 buttons and I have just assigned two side buttons to move the timeline.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/kpoviv7"> /u/kpoviv7 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14792th/does_anyone_have_a_mouse_with_multiple_buttons_i/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14792th/does_anyone_have_a_mouse_with_multiple_buttons_i/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14792th/does_anyone_have_a_mouse_with_multiple_buttons_i/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:38:54 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>NY vs LA?</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14744nz/ny_vs_la/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Whats the temperature right now in editing work for NY vs LA? Been out on the west coast for 14 years and looking to try out NY. Right now all my clients are remote, or fly me to location.</p> <p>Wondering how the work is in NY? Is it a strong market ? What type of work should I expect out there vs LA?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/futurespacecadet"> /u/futurespacecadet </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14744nz/ny_vs_la/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14744nz/ny_vs_la/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/14744nz/ny_vs_la/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:18:01 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>DNxHR export of RED Raw is 1 frame of on some files?</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1471riu/dnxhr_export_of_red_raw_is_1_frame_of_on_some/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>When I export DNxHR 444 12-bit (8K) from DaVinci of my graded RED Raw files I get some of the clips 1 frame off. It affects around 20-25% of the exported files. And they're all 1 frame off in the same direction, starting 1 frame earlier and ending 1 frame earlier.</p> <p>I've checked this by re-importing them back in DaVinci and they're 1 frame off there as well.</p> <p>Has anyone experienced something similar and knows a fix? There are more than 1000+ files I have to go through and re-export with 1 frame handles if there are no better solutions...</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/FinalPeasant"> /u/FinalPeasant </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1471riu/dnxhr_export_of_red_raw_is_1_frame_of_on_some/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1471riu/dnxhr_export_of_red_raw_is_1_frame_of_on_some/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1471riu/dnxhr_export_of_red_raw_is_1_frame_of_on_some/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 18:46:37 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>New BenQ SW272U for full screen edit / grading</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146tp40/new_benq_sw272u_for_full_screen_edit_grading/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>So, saw a new monitor pop up the other day. BenQ SW272U.</p> <p><a href="https://www.benq.com/en-us/monitor/professional/sw272u.html">https://www.benq.com/en-us/monitor/professional/sw272u.html</a></p> <p>Appears to be a successor to the SW271C (which I wasn't crazy about). The new model definitely specs out better on brightness and hopefully does a better job with uniformity.</p> <p>They do check all the boxes as far as on board hardware hosted calibration, 3D luts, and compatibility with ColourSpace / Calman.</p> <p>Still searching for a low cost monitor to slap into a few Premiere edit suites to get relatively accurate color for full screen edit output and color grading. In a MacOS environment these would be driven by Black Magic Ultra Studio Mini 4k. In a PC environment we may try direct from the GPU using Mercury Transmit.</p> <p>Going to try a few of these. Will report back.</p> <p>If anyone else grabs one, please share your thoughts.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/cammatador"> /u/cammatador </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146tp40/new_benq_sw272u_for_full_screen_edit_grading/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146tp40/new_benq_sw272u_for_full_screen_edit_grading/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146tp40/new_benq_sw272u_for_full_screen_edit_grading/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 13:15:52 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Another post about audio syncing sans PluralEyes</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146sa7n/another_post_about_audio_syncing_sans_pluraleyes/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi there,</p> <p>I work on a show with lots and lots of multicam verite footage, most of which is shot with scratch sound but without jam-sync. How are people dealing with building sync maps for these scenarios? We use Avid, and when there is TOD TC it's easy to just autosequence and lay up the cameras. However, often there's at least one source (drone, GoPro, DSLR or mirrorless) that doesn't match up.</p> <p>In the old days I would use PluralEyes, but it's a bit cumbersome now to keep one old Mac kicking around running Mojave so we can use it just for syncing. If that's the only solution, so be it, but I haven't found any sync-by-waveform feature that will spit out a syncmap for me the way that PluralEyes will.</p> <p>My ideal scenario is if Resolve has this feature without my knowledge. I know it has AutoAlign, which is close, but often the by-waveform function is iffy, and doing things clip-by-clip is not great for the grab-and-go shooting in my show. Often we have hundreds of clips per reel, and it's difficult to know if one small shot goes with external audio, B or C cam, or nothing at all. Not to mention if TOD TC exists, but a few clips were recorded before the shooter remembered, and we don't realize until half way through syncing...</p> <p>I've done searches on the sub for this, and while a lot of people have asked, most of the responses seem to be that the tools that exist now are adequate. What am I missing here? My AEs can take a full day to sync one day of footage, and we have hundreds of shoot days.</p> <p>Any help would be greatly appreciated.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/ReelBack96"> /u/ReelBack96 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146sa7n/another_post_about_audio_syncing_sans_pluraleyes/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146sa7n/another_post_about_audio_syncing_sans_pluraleyes/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146sa7n/another_post_about_audio_syncing_sans_pluraleyes/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 12:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Working on proxy files with no original footage?</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146nrb4/working_on_proxy_files_with_no_original_footage/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Client shoots in 4k. We’re both on Final Cut, he does the exporting himself. </p> <p>I received the files in 1080 proxy. My question is, can I edit as normal and send it back as xml for him to export it or do I need to do anything in settings with the proxy files so that he can then remove proxy and export in 4k without losing quality? </p> <p>Thanks in advance</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/TheVideoLad"> /u/TheVideoLad </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146nrb4/working_on_proxy_files_with_no_original_footage/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146nrb4/working_on_proxy_files_with_no_original_footage/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146nrb4/working_on_proxy_files_with_no_original_footage/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 07:44:36 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>FCPYoutubeChapters plugin needs your feedback!</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146ikgk/fcpyoutubechapters_plugin_needs_your_feedback/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Hi,<br /> I'm the creator of FCPYoutubeChapters which lets you create youtube chapters directly inside Final Cut.<br /> I use this tool myself every time I make a long youtube video, but I'm not sure if it works for you. For example, I don't have an M1 Mac, and I don't use really complex timelines.<br /> I would like to have your feedback so I can make my project better for everyone.</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/perecastor"> /u/perecastor </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146ikgk/fcpyoutubechapters_plugin_needs_your_feedback/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146ikgk/fcpyoutubechapters_plugin_needs_your_feedback/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146ikgk/fcpyoutubechapters_plugin_needs_your_feedback/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 02:50:40 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Does anyone know how to make this vegetation effect around the video synthesia?</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146hgkk/does_anyone_know_how_to_make_this_vegetation/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4dfgeyk2svU">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4dfgeyk2svU</a></p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Ok_Whole692"> /u/Ok_Whole692 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146hgkk/does_anyone_know_how_to_make_this_vegetation/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146hgkk/does_anyone_know_how_to_make_this_vegetation/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/146hgkk/does_anyone_know_how_to_make_this_vegetation/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 01:52:47 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>On Screen Text for VFX/Sound Notes</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1467vt0/on_screen_text_for_vfxsound_notes/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Is there a “standard” way to include on screen VFX/SFX/ADR notes while you’re working on a rough cut? </p> <p>I’ve seen it done various ways but was curious what you all do? I know a lot of that has been moved to Frame.io, Vimeo, etc… but for this project we’d like everything on screen.</p> <p>Thanks!</p> <p>Premiere Pro 23</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Yeah3846ok"> /u/Yeah3846ok </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1467vt0/on_screen_text_for_vfxsound_notes/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1467vt0/on_screen_text_for_vfxsound_notes/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1467vt0/on_screen_text_for_vfxsound_notes/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 18:48:49 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            <item>
                <title>Google Maps</title>
                <link>https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1466k0l/google_maps/</link>
                <description><!-- SC_OFF --><div class="md"><p>Need some vectorized maps for a Google spec spot I’m cutting as there are some pretty massive zooms in/out + transitions of locations on Google maps. I tried using Snazzy Maps and vectorizing them in Illustrator but they always end up looking cartoon-ish. Anyone have a good way of doing this?</p> </div><!-- SC_ON --> &#32; submitted by &#32; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Jschwartz567"> /u/Jschwartz567 </a> <br /> <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1466k0l/google_maps/">[link]</a></span> &#32; <span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1466k0l/google_maps/">[comments]</a></span></description>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.reddit.com/r/editors/comments/1466k0l/google_maps/</guid>
                <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 17:52:46 GMT</pubDate>
            </item>
            </channel>
    </rss>